Guide to the Sam di Bonaventura papers, 1900-1998
George Mason University Libraries
- Dr. Sam di Bonaventura papers
  - Composers Sj-Spo [1961-1982] (Box 45)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Skalkottas, 2.Skilton (EMPTY), 3.Slavenski, 4.Smalley, 5.Smart, 6.Smit, 7.Smith, G., 8.Smith, H., 9.Smith, J.C., 10.Smith, M., 11.Smith, R., 12.Smith, Sid., 13.Smith, Stu., 14.Snitzler, 15.Snow, 16.Sobelewski, 17.Soderini, 18.Solage, 19.Soler, 20.Sollberger, 21.Somers, 22.Sommer, 23.Soproni, 24.Sor, 25.Sorabji, 26.Soriano, 27.Sousa, 28.Souster, 29.Sowerby, 30.Speer, 31.Spelman, 32.Sperger, 33.Sperindio, 34.Spies, 35.Spinacino, 36.Spindler, 37.Spinner, 38.Spisak, 39.Spohr, 40.Spontini Dates of materials: 1961, 1968, 1974, 1976, 1981, 1982
  - Composers S-Sche [1962-1984] (Box 45)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Sacchini, 2.Unlalbled (Sacco), 3.Sachs, H., 4.Saeverud, 5.Saguer, 6.Saint- Georges, 7.Saint-Luc, 8.Sala, 9.Salieri, 10.Sallinen, 11.Salzedo, 12.Salzman, 13.Saminsky, 14.Sammartini, 15.Samuel, 16.Sancho, 17.Sanders, J., 18.Sanders, R., 19.Sanjuan, 20.Sankey, 21.Santa Cruz, 22.Santa-Maria, 23.Santoro, 24.Santorsola, 25.Santos, 26.Sanz, 27.Saperstein, 28.Sapp, 29.Sarasate, 30.Sarmientos, 31.Sarri, 32.Sarti, 33.Sartorio, 34.Sartorius, 35.Sary, 36.Sauguet, 37.Sauter, 38.Savioni, 39.Saxe, 40.Scandello, 41.Schafer, 42.Schaffer, 43.Schat, 44.Schauensee, 45.Scheidemann, 46.Schenk (EMPTY), 47.Schenker Dates of materials: 1962, 1967, 1978, 1984
  - Composers Sta-Ste [1959-1981] (Box 46)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Staden (EMPTY), 2.Staden, S.G., 3.Staden, S.T., 4.Stadlmair, 5.Stainer, 6.Stanford, 7.Stanley, C.J., 8.Starer, 9.Stark, 10.Starzer, 11.Stasney, 12.Steele, 13.Steffani, 14.Steg, 15.Steibelt, 16.Steigleder (EMPTY), 17.Stekel, 18.Stenhammer, 19.Sternhold, 20.Stevens, H., 21.Stevenson Dates of materials: 1959, 1968, 1975, 1981
  - Composers Sti-Stu [1961-1988] (Box 46)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Still, 2.Stilman-Lasansky, 3.Stock, 4.Stockem, 5.Stoerl, 6.Stokes, 7.Stolzer, 8.Stolz (EMPTY), 9.Storace, 10.Stout, 11.Straight, 12.Strakosch, 13.Stranensky, 14.Stratico, 15.Strayhorn, 16.Strengthfield, 17.Striggio, 18.Strilko, 19.Strogers, 20.Strong, 21.Strozzi, G., 22.Strungk, D. (EMPTY), 23.Strungk, N. (EMPTY), 24.Stuart, 25.Stuck Dates of materials: 1961, 1975, 1988
  - Composers Su-Sz [1960-1981] (Box 46)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Subotnick, 2.Sudds, 3.Suderburg, 4.Suesse, 5.Summerlin, 6.Suppeacute;, 7.Sur, 8.Surinach, 9.Susa, 10.Susato, 11.Susskind, 12.Suter, 13.Sutermeister, 14.Svendsen, 15.Sviridov, 16.Swan, 17.Swift, 18.Swing, 19.Sydeman, 20.Syrinx, 21.Szabelski, 22.Szabolesi, 23.Szekely, 24.Szeligowski, 25.Szokolay, 26.Szollosy, 27.Szulc, 28.Szymanowski Dates of materials: 1960, 1967, 1976, 1981
  - Composers Ta-Te [1963-1982] (Box 46)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Tadinghen (EMPTY), 2.Tailleferre, 3.Takacs, 4.Takahashi, 5.Takata, 6.Takemitsu, 7.Taktakishvili, 8.Tal, 9.Tallis, 10.Tamkin, 11.Taneyev, 12.Tansman, 13.Tapissier, 14.Tapray, 15.Tartaglini, 16.Tartini, 17.Taskin, 18.Taubert, 19.Tauriello, 20.Tausinger, 21.Taverner, 22.Taverner, J., 23.Taylor, C., 24.Taylor, D., 25.Teitelbaum, 26.Templeton, 27.Tenney, 28.Teppa, 29.Tepper, 30.Terradellas, 31.Tessarini, 32.Tessier, 33.Teszleri Dates of materials: 1963, 1965, 1972, 1982
  - Composers Th-Tl [1968-1985] (Box 47)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Thalberg, 2.Thatcher, 3.Theile, 4.Themmen, 5.Thomas, A., 6.Thomas, C.E., 7.Thomas, K., 8.Thompson, 9.Thomson, A., 10.Thomson, V., 11.Thomson, W., 12.Thorne, 13.Tinctoris, 14.Tippett, 15.Tillis, 16.Tischhauser, 17.Tishchenko, 18.Titelouze Dates of materials: 1968, 1972-73, 1981, 1985
  - Composers To-Tz [1966-1982] (Box 47)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Toch,2.Toeschi, 3.Tomkins, 4.Torelli, 5.Torme, 6.Torroba, 7.Tosar, 8.Tournemire, 9.Tours, 10.Tower, 11.Trabacci, 12.Traetta, 13.Travis, 14.Trebor, 15.Trimble, 16.Trombly, 17.Tromboncino, 18.Trotter, 19.Trythall, 20.Tubin, 21.Tudor, 22.Tufts, 23.Tull, 24.Tunder, 25.Tuotilo, 26.Turina, J., 27.Turini, 28.Turner, T., 29.Turnhout (EMPTY), 30.Turok, 31.Tuthill, 32.Tye, 33.Tyes Dates of materials: 1966, 1970, 1976, 1981, 1982
  - Composers U-Va [1959-1980] (Box 47)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Uber, 2.Ubieta, 3.Uccellini, 4.Uhl, 5.Ulehla, 6.Ultan, 7.Ung, 8.Urspruch, 9.Ussachevsky, 10.Vaet, 11.Vaillant, 12.Valcarcel, 13.Valderrabang, 14.Valen, 15.Valente, 16.Valentine, 17.Vanhall, 18.Van Heusen, 19.Vanhurenbeck, 20.Van Vlijmen, 21.Vardell, 22.Vardi Dates of materials: 1959, 1964, 1968, 1978, 1980
  - Composers Ve-Vic [1966-1981] (Box 47)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Vecchi, 2.Vega, Aurelio de la, 3.Velut, 4.Veracini, A., 5.Vercini, F., 6.Verdelot, 7.Vernon, 8.Vernor, 9.Verrall, 10.Veress, 11.Viadana, 12.Viardot-Garcia, 13.Vicentino, 14.Victoria Dates of materials: 1966, 1981
  - Composers Vie-Vz [1962-1978] (Box 48)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Vierdanck, 2.Vierne, 3.Vieuxtemps, 4.Viguerie, 5.Vincent, 6.Vinci, 7.Viotti, 8.Virdung, 9.Vitali, G.B., 10.Vitali, T.A., 11.Vittori, 12.Vogel, 13.Voit, 14.Volkonsky, 15.Vorisek, 16.Vulpius (EMPTY), 17.Vyschnegradsky Dates of materials: 1962, 1966, 1971, 1977, 1978
  - Composers Wa-Wee [1964-1982] (Box 48)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Wagoner, 2.Waelrant, 3.Wagenaar, 4.Wagenseil, 5.Waldteufel, 6.Walker, D., 7.Walker, G., 8.Walker, T., 9.Waller, 10.Walmisley, 11.Walter, J., 12.Walter, T., 13.Walther, J.G., 14.Walther, J.J., 15.Wanski, 16.Ward, E., 17.Ward, H., 18.Ward, R, 19.Ward-Steinman, 20.Warlock, 21.Warren, Ray, 22.Wartensee, 23.Washburn, 24.Washington, 25.Waters, 26.Waxman, Don, 27.Webb, 28.Webbe, Samuel (EMPTY), 19.Weber, Ben, 20.Weber, H., 21.Weckmann, 22.Weeks, 23.Weelkes Dates of materials: 1964, 1968, 1971, 1981, 1982
  - Composers Wei-Wh [1962-1980] (Box 48)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Weigl, 2.Weinberg, H., 3.Weinberg, J., 4.Weinberger, 5.Weiner, L., 6.Weiner, S., 7.Weingartner, 8.Weinzweig, 9.Weisgall, 10.Weiss, A., 11.Weiss, Silvius, 12.Welcher, 13.Weldon, J. (EMPTY), 14.Welin, 15.Wellesz, 16.Welwood, 17.Wen- Chung, 18.Werckmeister, 19.Werle, 20.Werner, 21.Wernick, 22.Werren, 23.Werth, Jacob Van, 24.Wesley, C., 25.Wesley, S., 26.Weyse, 27.Whear, 28.Whettam, 29.White, D., 30.White, M., 31.White, R., 32.Whiting, A., 33.Whittenberg Dates of materials: 1962, 1980
  - Composers Wis-Wz [1959-1982] (Box 48)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Wise, M. (EMPTY), 2.Witkin, 3.Woelfl, 4.Wohlgemuth, 5.Wolf, Hugo, 6.Wolff, C., 7.Wolf-Ferrari, 8.Wolkenstein, 9.Wolpe, 10.Wonder, 11.Wood, 12.Woodcock, 13.Woodward, 14.Woollen, 15.Work, 16.Worley, 17.Worsdale, 18.Wright, M., 19.Wuorinen, 20.Wykes, 21.Wyner, 22.Wyttenbach Dates of materials: 1959, 1969, 1972, 1981, 1982
  - Composers Wi-Wir [1966-1981] (Box 49)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Widmann, 2.Widor, 3.Wieniawski, 4.Wieslander, 5.Wigglesworth, 6.Wilbye, 7.Wild, 8.Wildberger, 9.Wilder, 10.Willaert, 11.Willan, 12.Williams, L., 13.Williams, P., 14.Williamson, 15.Wills, 16.Wilson, D., 17.Wilson, J., 18.Wilson, M., 19.Wilson, O., 20.Wilson, R., 21.Wiren Dates of materials: 1966, 1972, 1975, 1981
  - Composers X-Z [1962-1982] (Box 49)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Xenakis, 2.Yardumian, 3.Yarrow, 4.Yashito, 5.Yasser, 6.York, 7.Young, D., 8.Ysaye, 9.Yttrehus, 10.Yuasa, 11.Yun, Isang, 12.Yurko, 13.Yvain, 14.Zacharias, Mag., 15.Zacher, Gerd, 16.Zachow, 17.Zaleucus, 18.Zandonai, 19.Zarlino, 20.Zelter, K.F., 21.Zemlinsky, 22.Ziani, 23.Zielenski, 24.Zimmermann, 25.Zipoli, 26.Zummo, 27.Zumsteeg, 28.Zupko, 29.Zwierzchowski Dates of materials: 1962, 1976, 1982
  - Composers Concerto 1967 (Box 49)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1. 10 (Class No. 10: I. Handel, Six Oboe Concertos, II. Bach: Goldberg Variations, III. Bach: Orchestral Suites), 2. 11 (Class No. 11: I. Bach: Well-Tempered Klavier, II. Bach: Sinfonie a3, III. Bach: Passacaglia and Fugue), 3. 12 (Class No. 12: I. Anon: Lute and its Repertoire, II. Bach: Italian Concerto, III. Bach: The Musical Offering), 4. 13 (Class No. 13: I. Handel: Six Violin Sonatas, II. Bach: Concerti for 2 Harpischords; III. Bach: 6 Trio Sonatas), 5. 14 (Class No. 14: I. Bach Orgelbuchlein; II. Bach: Suites for Solo Cello, III. Bach: Partitas for Harpsichord), 6. Unlabeled (Concerto misc.) Dates of materials: 1967
  - Concerto 2 1986 (Box 49)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly papers, Class outlines, Illustrations Headings: 1. Calendar, 2.Music Exx (EMPTY), 3.Vocal Conc[ertos] (Viadana; Schuetz; Schein; Scheidt; Grandi; Monteverdi), 4.Resources (Keyboard: 17-18th C.; Winds: 17th- 18th c.; Violin: 17th-18th c.; Piano: 19th c.; Violin: 19th c.; Winds: 19th-20th c.; Organ: 20th c.; Harpsichord: 20th c.; Piano: 20th c.; Violin: 20th c.; Bach; Beethoven; Brahms; Handel; Haydn; Liszt; Mendelssohn; Mozart; Telemann; Vivaldi) Dates of materials: 1986
  - Concerto A-Y (Box 49)
    Content: Notes Headings: None. Notes on soloists and composers with last names A-Y concerning the classical concerto. Dates of materials: ?
  - Copland I [1946-1988] (Box 50)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Choral Misc., 5.Complete Works, 6.Concerto, 7.Dance, 8.Fantasia, 9.Film Music, 10.Incidental Music, 11.Instrumental Misc. (EMPTY), 12.Letters (EMPTY), 13.Literary Dates of materials: 1946, 1969, 1985, 1988
  - Copland II [1966-1988] (Box 50)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Misc., 2.Motet (EMPTY), 3.Nonet, 4.Opera, 5.Orchestral Misc., 6.Organ Misc. (EMPTY), 7.Overture, 8.Passacaglia, 9.Piano Misc., 10.Prelude, 11.Quartet (EMPTY), 12.Sextet, 13.Sonata, 14.Song, 15.Style, 16.Suite, 17.Symphony, 18.Trio, 19.Variation Dates of materials: 1966, 1976, 1984, 1988
  - Couperin [1951-1979] (Box 50)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Couperin, Francois, 2.Couperin, Louis (1626-61) Dates of materials: 1951, 1960, 1971, 1979
  - Cowell [1963-1986] (Box 50)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: None (Cowell: Orch. Misc; Cowell: Quartet; Cowell: Piano Misc.; Cowell: Symphony; Cowell: Hymn; Cowell: Complete Works) Dates of materials: 1963-64, 1976, 1986
  - Creston/Crumb [1968-1981] (Box 51)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Creston, Paul (1906-), 2.Crumb, George Dates of materials: 1968, 1973, 1976, 1981
  - Dallapiccola/Delius [1951-1977] (Box 51)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Dallapiccola, L. (1904-), 2.Delius, Frederick (1862-1934) Dates of materials: 1951, 1977
  - Debussy I [1962-1984] (Box 51)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Ballet, 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Cantata, 5.Chamber Misc., 6.Choral Misc., 7.Complete Works, 8.Dance, 9.Etude, 10.Fantasia, 11.Incidental Music, 12.Instr. Misc., 13.Letters, 14.Literary, 15.Misc., 16.Nocturne, 17.Opera, 18.Orch. Misc. Dates of materials: 1962, 1970, 1977, 1984
  - Debussy II [1953-1976] (Box 51)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Piano Misc., 2.Prelude, 3.Quartet, 4.Rhapsody, 5.Sonata, 6.Song, 7.Style, 8.Suite, 9.Tone Poem Dates of materials: 1953, 1976
  - Delibes/Dello Joio/Del Tredici [1979-1985] (Box 52)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Delibes, Leo, 2.Dello Joio, 3.Del Tredici Dates of materials: 1979, 1982, 1985
  - Donizetti I [1959-1981] (Box 52)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Bibliography, 2.Biography, 3.Cantata, 4.Chamber Music, 5.Complete Works, 6.Letters (EMPTY), 7.Mass, 8.Misc., 9.Nonet, 10.Oratorio, 11.Orchestral Misc., 12.Piano Music, 13.Sacred Music, 14.Style, 15.Vocal Music, 16.Adelasia (EMPTY), 17.Ajo (EMPTY), 18.Alahor (EMPTY), 19.Alfredo Il Grande (EMPTY), 20.Anna Bolena, 21.Aristea (EMPTY), 22.Belisario, 23.Betly (EMPTY), 24.Borgomestro (EMPTY), 25.Campanello, 26.Castello Inval. (EMPTY), 27.Castello Kenil.(EMPTY), 28.Catarina Cornaro, 29.Chiara/Serafina (EMPTY), 30.Convenienzi (EMPTY), 31.Diluvio (EMPTY), 32.Dom Sebastien, 33.Don Pasquale, 34.Duca dAlba, 35.Elisabetta/Kenil. (EMPTY), 36.Elisir Dates of materials: 1959, 1966, 1974, 1981
  - Donizetti II [1964-1986] (Box 52)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Elvida (EMPTY), 2.Emilia (EMPTY), 3.Enrico di Borg. (EMPTY), 4.Esule de Roma (EMPTY), 5.Falegnamo (EMPTY), 6.Fausta (EMPTY), 7.Favorita, 8.Fille du Regiment, 9.Follia, Una (EMPTY), 10.Fortunato (EMPTY), 11.Francesca (EMPTY), 12.Furioso, 13.Gabriella (EMPTY), 14.Gemma di Vergy (EMPTY), 15.Gianni di Calais (EMPTY), 16.Gianni di Parigi (EMPTY), 17.Giovedi Grasso, 18.Isnelda (EMPTY), 19.Lettera, La (EMPTY), 20.Linda, 21.Lucia, 22.Lucrezia Borgia, 23.Maria Padilla (EMPTY), 24.Maria di Rohan, 25.Maria di Rudenz (EMPTY), 26.Maria Stuarda, 27.Marino Faliero, 28.Misc., 29.Nozze in Villa (EMPTY), 30.Nuovo Pource. (EMPTY), 31.Olivo/Pasquale (EMPTY), 32.Otto Mese (EMPTY), 33.Paria (EMPTY), 34.Parisina, 35.Pazzi (EMPTY), 36.Pia di Tolomei, 37.Pigmalione (EMPTY), 38.Poliuto, 39.Regina (EMPTY), 40.Rita, 41.Roberto, 42.Romanziera (EMPTY), 43.Rosamunda (EMPTY), 44.Sancia (EMPTY), 45.Torquato Tasso (EMPTY), 46.Ugo (EMPTY), 47.Zingara (EMPTY), 48.Zoraide (EMPTY) Dates of materials: 1964, 1980, 1986
  - Dowland/Drckman/Dukas [1963-1980] (Box 52)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Dowland, 2.Druckman, 3.Dukas Dates of materials: 1963, 1968, 1976, 1980
  - Dufay I 1970 (Box 53)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Antiphon, 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Chanson, 4.Complete Works, 5.Hymn, 6.Magnificat Dates of materials: 1970
  - Dufay II 1970 (Box 53)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Mass, 2.Misc., 3.Motet, 4.Style Dates of materials: 1970
  - Dunstable 1968 (Box 53)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: None- fills one 1" binder (Dunstable: Style; Dunstable: Magnificat; Dunstable: Motet; Dunstable: Hymn) Dates of materials: 1968
  - Dvorak [1967-1981] (Box 53)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Bibliography (EMPTY), 2.Biography, 3.Chamber Misc., 4.Choral Misc., 5.Complete Works, 6.Concerto, 7.Dance, 8.Instrumental Misc. (EMPTY), 9.Letters, 10.Literary (EMPTY), 11.Mass, 12.Miscellaneous, 13.Opera, 14.Orchestral Misc., 15.Overture, 16.Piano Misc. (EMPTY), 17.Quartet, 18.Quintet, 19.Rhapsody (EMPTY), 20.Scherzo, 21.Serenade, 22.Sextet, 23.Sonata, 24.Song, 25.Stabat Mater, 26.Style, 27.Suite, 28.Tone Poem, 29.Trio, 30.Variation Dates of materials: 1967, 1971, 1981
  - Dvorak Symphony [1972-1982] (Box 53)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs, Class Outlines Headings: 1.Misc. (Dvorak Symphony), 2.No. I, 3.No. II (EMPTY), 4.No. III (EMPTY), 5.No. IV, 6.No. V (EMPTY), 7.No. VI, 8.No. VII, 9.No. VIII, 10.No. IX Dates of materials: 1972, 1976, 1982
  - Elgar [1968-1981] (Box 54)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Ballet (EMPTY), 2.Bibliography (EMPTY), 3.Biography, 4.Cantata (EMPTY), 5.Choral Misc., 6.Complete Works, 7.Concerto, 8.Etude (EMPTY), 9.Incidental Music, 10.Instrumental Misc., 11.Letters (EMPTY), 12.Literary, 13.March (EMPTY), 14.Misc., 15.Motet (EMPTY), 16.Ode (EMPTY), 17.Opera (EMPTY), 18.Oratorio, 19.Orch.Misc., 20.Organ Misc. (EMPTY), 21.Overture, 22.Prelude (EMPTY), 23.Psalm (EMPTY), 24.Quartet (EMPTY), 25.Quintet, 26.Sacred Misc., 27.Serenade, 28.Sonata (EMPTY), 29.Song (EMPTY), 30.Style, 31.Suite (EMPTY), 32.Symphony, 33.Te Deum (EMPTY), 34.Tone Poem, 35.Variation Dates of materials: 1968, 1975, 1981
  - Ellington [1966-1977] (Box 54)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Concert Programs Headings: None- materials fill one 1" binder (Ellington: Biography; Ellington: Song; Ellington: Misc.; Ellington: Orch. Misc.; Ellington: Ballet) Dates of materials: 1966-1977
  - Europe [1966-1972] (Box 54)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.European, 2.Albania (EMPTY), 3.Andorra (EMPTY), 4.Austria, 5.Belgium, 6.Bulgaria (EMPTY), 7.Czech, 8.Unlabeled (Denmark), 9.England, 10.Finland, 11.France, 12.Unlabeled (Germany), 13.Germany: West, 14.Hungary, 15.Iceland (EMPTY), 16.Ireland, 17.Unlabeled (Italy), 18.Liechtenstein (EMPTY), 19.Luxembourg, 20.Monaco Dates of materials: 1966-1972
  - Falla/Faure [1968-1991] (Box 54)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.Falla, Manuel de (1876-1946) [Ballet; Biography; Concerto; Literary; Song; Suite; Opera; Nocturne), 2.Faur, Gabriel (1845-1924) [Requiem; Opera; Faureacute;; Piano Music; Style; Vocal Misc.; Song; Incidental Music; Ballette; Mass; Fantasia; Piano Misc.; Trio) Dates of materials: 1968, 1977, 1982, 1988, 1991
  - Farina/Fontana/Frescobaldi 1971 (Box 54)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Farina, Carlo, 2.Fontana, Giov.Batt. (-1630) Dates of materials: 1971
  - Film Music I (Box 55)
    Content: Notes on film music Headings: A-Z dividers. Material on film music/film music composers fills one 1" binder Dates of materials: ?
  - Folk I [1976-1980] (Box 55)
    Content: Class Notes, Articles, Notes Headings: 1.Class Plans, 2.Outlines, 3.Definition, 4.Polynesia, 5.Common Characteristics, 6.Meter, 7.American, 8.Arrangements, 9.Spiritual, 10.Gospel Song, 11.Railroads, 12.French, 13.Recordings, 14.Importance Dates of materials: 1976, 1980
  - Folk 2 (Box 55)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1. Nationalism (Outlines; Definition; Exoticism; Recordings; Importance), 2.Instruments (Classification; Pictures; Folkways; Streisand; Orchestrion; Penn; Partch; Britten; Theremin; Moog; Electronic Music; Electrophones; Pictures; Orchestra; Consort; Dates of materials: ?
  - Folk 3 [1979-1981] (Box 55)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.Miscellaneous, 2.Sea Shanties, 3.Addiss-Crofut, 4.Falla: Song, 5.American (Description), 6.American (Outline), 7.American (Recordings), 8.Hymns, 9.Spirituals, 10.Railroads, 11.Ballad, 12.Gospel Song, 13.Topkapi Dates of materials: 1979, 1981
  - Folk 4 (Box 55)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Illustrations Headings: 1.Instruments: Beginning, 2.Instruments: Classification, 3.Instruments: Orchestra, 4.Venice, 5.Instruments: Pix, 6.Orchestra: Seating, 7.Instruments: String Makers, 8.Instruments: Usage, 9.Instrs: Folkways, 10.Instrs: Streisand, 11.Instrs: Electronic, 12.Orchestration, 13.Instruments: Organ, 14.Instruments: Moog, 15.Instruments: Penn, 16.Instruments: Partch Dates of materials: ?
  - Form C-R [1915-1953] (Box 55)
    Content: Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.General, 2.Canon, 3.Cantus Firmus, 4.Canzona, 5.Capriccio, 6.Chaconne, 7.Chamber Music, 8.Concerto, 9.Counterpoint, 10.Cyclic, 11.Divirtimento, 12.Etude, 13.Fantasia, 14.Formes Fixes, 15.Fugue, 16.Ground, 17.Incidental Music (EMPTY), 18.Invention (EMPTY), 19.Minuet, 20.Misc., 21.Overture, 22.Partita (EMPTY), 23.Passacaglia, 24.Prelude, 25.Program Music, 26.Rhapsody, 27.Ricercar, 28.Ritornello (EMPTY), 29.Romance Dates of materials: 1915, 1953
  - Form I (Box 56)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Binary, 2.Ternary, 3.Rondo, 4.Sonata-Allegro, 5.Canon, 6.Fugue, 7.Variation, 8.Passacaglia, 9.Chaconne, 10.Performer, 11.Misc. Dates of materials: ?
  - Form II 1994 (Box 56)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Binary, 2.Ternary, 3.Rondo, 4.Sonata-Allegro, 5.Canon, 6.Fugue, 7.Passacaglia, 8.Chaconne, 9.Variation, 10.Choral Forms, 11.Free Forms, 12.Homophonic I, 13.Homophonic II, 14.Multi Movement, 15.Polyphonic, 16.Program Music, 17.Song Forms Dates of materials: 1994
  - Form III [1915-1953] (Box 56)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Variation, 2.Voluntary, 3.Round, 4.Scherzo, 5.Serenade, 6.Sinfonia, 7.Sinfonietta, 8.Sonata, 9.Sonata-Rondo (EMPTY), 10.Sonatina, 11.Strophic, 12.Suite, 13.Symphony, 14.Toccata, 15.Rondo Dates of materials: 1915, 1953
  - Form IV (Box 56)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: None (Form)- fills one 1" binder Dates of materials: ?
  - Form V (Box 56)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: None (Binary Form)- fills one 1" binder Dates of materials: ?
  - Form Misc. 1953 (Box 56)
    Content: Articles Headings: None ("Dramatic Forms" from Musical Forms amp; Textures by Demuth (1953) Dates of materials: 1953
  - Form- Classical [1888-1898] (Box 57)
    Content: Notes, Articles Headings: 1.None (Schematic Representation of Evolution from Binary to Sonata- Allegro Form), 2.Benward, 3.Spencer Dates of materials: 1988, 1998
  - Foss/Franck [1965-1979] (Box 57)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Foss, Lucas (1922-) (Orchestral Misc.; Variation; Choral Misc.; Instrumental Misc.; Concerto; Foss; Songs; Improvisation; Cantata; Piano Misc. Choral Works; Orchestral Misc; Misc.; Biography; Litarary; Etude; Ballet), 2.Franck, Cesar (1822-90) (Franck Symphony; Trio; Tone Poem; Organ Music; Biography) Dates of materials: 1965, 1970, 1975, 1979
  - Frattole/Stambotti (Box 57)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: 1.None (Harmony), 2.Misc. Caralogues, 3.Manuscripts Sources, 4.Modena a.F.9.9. (A Description of Codex a.F.9.9. Modena, Biblioteca Estense), 5.Strambotti, 6. "Sheets" (Musical Scores), 7."Examples" (Musical Scores), 8.Transcriptions Bk IV, 9.Transcriptions Book V (EMPTY), 10.Transcriptions Bk VI, 11.Transcriptions Bk VII (EMPTY), 12.Transcriptions Book VIII, Transcriptions Book IX Dates of materials: ?
  - Gabrieli 1966 (Box 57)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Gabrieli, Andrea (c.1510-86) Dates of materials: 1966
  - Geminiani/Gounod [1958-1978] (Box 58)
    Content: Notes, Articles, Musical Scores, Concert Programs Headings: 1.Gounod, Charles (1818-93)(Opera, Mass, March), 2.Geminiani, Francesco (1674-1762)(Concerto) Dates of materials: 1958, 1964, 1978
  - Gerhard [1956-1961] (Box 58)
    Content: Articles Headings: None (Gerhard; Concerto; Biography; Capriccio; Incidental Music; Orch. Music; Style; Biography; Complete Works) Dates of materials: 1956, 1961
  - Gershwin [1967-1985] (Box 58)
    Content: Articles, Notes Headings: None (Rhapsody; Biography; Gershwin; Opera; Musical; Tone Poem; Prelude; Concerto; Misc.; Style; Complete Works; Lullaby) Dates of materials: 1967, 1975, 1985
  - Gesualdo/Glazunov/Glinka [1968-1976] (Box 58)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Concert Programs, Musical Scores Headings: 1.Gesualdo (Misc.; Madrigal), 2.Glazunov (Works; Symphony; Concerto; Ballet), 3.Glinka (Opera; Biography) Dates of materials: 1968, 1976
  - Ginastera [1965-1986] (Box 59)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: None (Portrait; Biography; Discography; Complete Works; Psalm; Ginastera; Variation; Ballet; Opera; Overture; Orchestral Misc.; Sonata; Concerto) Dates of materials: 1965, 1986
  - Gluck [1964-1984] (Box 59)
    Content: Articles, Notes, Musical Scores Headings: None (Opera; Biography; Complete Works) Dates of materials: 1969, 1984
  - Gombert 1970 (Box 59)
    Content: Notes, Musical Scores, Scholarly Papers Headings: None (Motet; Mass; Magnificat; Complete Works) Dates of materials: 1970